In local news, rio arriba county sheriff
is still searching for the
forces that's involved in...
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You got a problem with something?
Look, I get it.
Most guys get awkward
after the fact.
Look, just drop it.
The wives almost never find out.
That's the last thing you should
be thinking about right now.
- You paying me or what?
- Every penny.
Here's the thing. I'm dropping
your ass off out here.
The hell you are! You said you
would drive me back to town.
You think I'd drop you off
in that fucking skirt
within 50 miles of the town I live in?
You think I'm fucking nuts?
You fucking asshole. It's the
middle of fucking nowhere!
You need to get the fuck out of my car.
Fuck you, bitch.
The fuck? You fucking promised!
What the fuck?
You're getting the fuck
out of my car!
You little dick motherfucker!
You fucking promised!
- Get your fucking ass out!
- What the fuck?
- Drive me back, motherfucker!
- Get your sleazy ass...
- No!
- Outta the fucking car.
- Do not fucking touch me!
- Hey!
- Get the fuck off!
- Get your fucking ass off!
- Fuck!
- Get the fuck outta here.
- Stop being a fucking pussy!
- Fuck you, bitch!
- You fucking hussy, bitch!
- Fuck you!
Hello?
Anyone in there?
Sweet.
You're four weeks
overdue, grace.
You know I've been trying to
get ahold of you for weeks now,
but you don't open the door.
That's just not respectful.
Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry.
It's just, uh, the payments have
been kind of hard to manage.
- It's been a struggle.
- I don't know.
I don't know.
What are we gonna do?
I was thinking...
And I was hoping I could
pawn some more stuff.
You're kidding me, right?
Look, I didn't even think you had
anything left in your apartment.
All right, what do you got?
Well, this is a piece of shit.
It's five gs.
And you're not making payments.
Grace...
What are we gonna do?
Mm.
It seems to me
that you can't pay.
Oh, well...
That's when we can start
getting creative.
I'm a reasonable man, grace.
Motherfuckers!
Those sick motherfuckers!
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Fill her up.
Hurry up!
- Come on.
- Hurry up.
- Okay, I'm doing it. I'm doing it!
- Let's go.
Good boy.
Oh, yeah.
I haven't got all fucking day.
Hurry up.
Okay, okay.
All right. Okay.
All right, good job.
- No, no, no! No!
- Okay.
What are you doing?
- Huh?
- He made me. Just bad luck, huh?
Are you fucking
out of your mind?
What do you think, soldier boy?
He's a kid.
It was unnecessary!
Well, he should have checked
his fucking horoscope.
No, no. Fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck!
Guys, get out here fast.
Get out here now!
Fuck!
Fuck! Chris left.
Chris fucking left, man.
He's out of here.
He left.
Jesus. Fuck!
Fuck!
You got a car?
Huh?
You're coming with us.
- I got a car.
- Well, let's go.
She's driving.
I didn't sign up for a hostage.
If the three of us get
pulled over by the cops,
shit goes south real quick.
She's driving, we're low
in the seats. That's it.
Fuck.
You're driving.
Fuck, shit.
Let's go. Go!
Lose the masks.
Wait. No. Please,
I can't see your faces.
It's all right.
I'm fine.
Like that kid was?
Oh, that's if you're lucky.
Do you wanna test your luck?
'Cause, uh, wait.
Hold on.
I got this little game
we could play.
Just please drive.
Or we leave your body
by the side of the road
with a thousand
fucking holes in it.
- Your choice.
- Yeah, what my brother said.
Tie it off.
Where do I tie it?
Above the opening.
Not too tight.
Wait. Where am I going?
It doesn't matter.
Drive the fucking car.
What's the plan, man?
We keep driving till we
figure our next move.
Can you get that bullet out?
I'll need to look at it first,
see where the entry point is,
see what I'm dealing with.
- That a yes?
- It's what I just said.
Shit.
What the fuck is that?
Roadblock.
What are we gonna do, man?
Start with shutting
the fuck up, Shane.
Make a left here.
Left now!
Make the call.
- Not yet.
- Not yet?
We have no getaway plan. We have his money.
Make the call.
I said I would call him
- when the job is done.
- The job is done.
Missing soon-to-be-dead
getaway driver,
one hostage? Yeah.
Doesn't sound very done to me.
Right. And whose
fucking fault is that?
Mine? Me? What are you... I didn't
know he was gonna fucking skirt off
- at the first sign of trouble, man.
- I didn't... - Shh.
You fucking blackmail me.
You got somebody
waiting for you at home?
No.
Nobody, huh?
No. Not anymore.
- Why are you slowing down?
- No, no, no!
No. No, no, no.
Come on, come on. No!
Oh, shit!
The car fucking stopped.
Brilliant observation, retard.
Now, what?
Now, we get out
of the fucking car.
What are you doing?
Well, the car's out.
We don't need her.
I didn't sign up for that.
I don't do civilians.
I do what I have to
to ensure a clean getaway.
You're not doing this
to our hostage.
You're awfully merciful.
Or maybe I just got
enough bad Karma.
Ain't we a couple
of silverbacks.
Look...
We're already fucked.
We keep her alive. At
least we got some leverage.
You like her, don't you?
Okay.
She's your baggage.
What's over there?
More than what's here.
Fucking walking?
Affirmative.
Unless you got yourself
a bicycle.
You help your brother,
I got the girl and the bag.
Roger that.
Come on.
Fucking slow down.
Fuck.
You didn't try to run.
Where would I go?
Good point.
Fuck.
- Fuck.
- Okay.
Where are you going, man?
Well, to be honest,
probably gonna blow
this guy's head off.
We talked about that.
No more bodies.
That doesn't give us
very many options, does it?
We stay camouflaged.
Hidden.
You've really got yourself into the
wrong line of work, haven't you?
Listen up, cowboy.
You want your brother fixed up?
Then for now,
we're playing this my way.
We don't have to turn this place
into the fucking o.K.
Corral unless we have to.
- Both of you, get in the shadows.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- You don't get to boss my fucking brother...
- Sit back, kid.
He got hired for a reason.
Three, four hours tops.
Then we're gone.
Let's go.
All right, motherfucker.
Let's see what you got.
What's your name, anyway?
Grace.
Look, grace.
You seem smart.
Here's what gonna happen
when we get in there.
You're gonna do what I say when I say it.
You'll be fine.
Right. Like those people
at the pawnshop?
I had nothing to do
with how that went down.
Yeah. But you didn't
stop it either.
Hi there.
Hello?
Yeah, I didn't mean
to startle you.
What are you doing here?
Well, we were hoping
you could help us.
Um, our car broke down
a couple of miles back.
- It did?
- Yeah. And, uh...
You wanna call someone?
Well, I talked to my brother.
It's gonna take him a
little while to come get us.
- Your brother?
- Yeah.
I mean, he said
about three or four hours.
It's just getting
a little chilly out there.
Oh.
I-I don't...
I mean, I'm not...
Are those farmhand houses?
Are those empty or...
Yeah. They're empty. There's
no farmhands here anymore.
Really?
'Cause we were just...
You know, my wife and I,
we just... we're dead tired.
We just wanted a place
to sit for a few hours,
and we'll get out
of your hair easy.
I don't... I don't think that's
a good idea. I mean, I...
What's your name, sweetheart?
- Danny.
Danny, look, uh, we're...
It's been a long night.
And... we're just
pretty beat.
I mean, my-my sister,
she's in the hospital,
and we're just trying
to get to her.
And we are just
exhausted. Right?
Look, it would... It
would just be a few hours.
I mean, you wouldn't even
notice that we're here.
Those rooms, they're...
They're in an awful way.
I mean, we wouldn't
cause you any trouble at all.
- I...
- And we'll be gone before you know it.
We're quiet as mice.
Really.
Just a few hours.
You won't know we're here.
Okay.
There you go.
Thank you.
Which one should we take?
Are they...
Um, any you like.
- You sure? Okay.
- Okay.
Why are you all alone?
Where's your parents?
Um... my grandpa,
but he's not around.
He's running errands.
Well, thank you again.
A few hours, right?
You got my word.
Have a good night.
Thank you, Danny.
- And?
- We got a room.
Who's in there?
Some kid, lives with his grandpa.
He's not home.
Hmm. Grandpa comes home early,
we might have a problem.
You know how grumpy old men are.
You wanna help your brother out?
It's your best shot, cocksucker.
Oh. Still got it.
Come on.
Fucking shit.
When the old geezer comes back,
we'll take his car,
send our little hostage
on a nice vacation,
and I'll call the boss.
You gonna fix my dying,
fucking brother or what?
- Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck!
- Hey! Shh!
Give me a fucking pillow
or a fucking warning first.
Huh, where is the fun
in that? Hold him.
Hold it. Hold it.
I can feel it.
It's a nine millimeter.
I can get it out.
All right.
I need your help.
I need you to hold him steady.
Sorry about the driver.
I didn't think he'd drive off like that.
Well, you vouched for him.
Yeah.
He's a stand-up guy.
- I thought he was solid.
- Just shut up.
You're being dumb and annoying,
acting like a big fucking
pussy since you got shot.
Give me your lighter.
He's gonna need antibiotics
fast, or he's fucked.
Okay. All right,
buddy. Hold on.
- Hold on.
- No! Fuck that!
This is gonna hurt, kid.
- It's gonna hurt a bit.
- Oh, shit!
- Hold him steady.
- I'm trying!
Hey. Stop fucking moving,
or I'll kill you myself.
Take it like a fucking man!
That's the spirit, pal!
It ain't forceps, but...
Fuck!
Don't move.
I got it. I got it.
I got it.
You gonna sew him up?
This is gonna be
the painful part.
Fuck you. Fuck you.
He's out.
I haven't seen him cry that much
since his boyfriend dumped him.
He's not dead.
He's just passed out.
- He's my brother.
- Oh, I know.
Will he be all right?
Maybe.
Kid needs meds.
So what were you doing
in that pawnshop anyway?
Why were you in the back?
Doesn't matter.
Almost...
No.
That kid in the barn...
I got a weird feeling.
Did you?
I mean, we were
a bunch of strangers
that just showed up
in the middle of the night.
Yeah, I know.
But still.
Something's wrong.
Surely we can call
your boss now, Alex.
You ran the logistics.
I decide when we call my boss.
Right now, that's not an option.
You gonna let your brother
lose his leg?
Beats the bush and daisies.
It was you that cost him
the leg anyway.
Really?
'Cause I was told
you were a professional.
We're killers, not accountants.
What do you want from my bedside manner?
A blowjob?
No. I'd take a little
logic from ya, Alex.
'Cause I'd like to make it
outta here in one piece.
How soon until we can move my
brother?
If we're walking,
a couple hours at least.
If we even
have that. Fuck!
Shit.
About 40 minutes afterward,
and did get in a shootout
with Chris Wright.
- What is it?
- Fuck.
The suspected getaway driver,
he was shot and killed.
Police are hoping to find
this woman
who is said to be
the hostage of the suspects.
Oh, wonderful.
- They haven't made our faces.
- They made hers.
- Hey...
- Hey, hey, sit!
She's a liability.
I thought you ex-military guys
were all about tactics.
This isn't feeling
very tactical to me.
If the cops showed up now, they'd
waste no time in killing us.
With her here, they won't.
I keep telling ya.
It's called leverage.
You know, I think he
must be your biggest fan.
All right. Well, we still
gotta deal with the boy.
We're waiting for grandpa,
remember?
That was before we saw the news.
Right now, the kid could be on
the phone, squealing to the cops.
I'm just gonna
make sure he's not.
You're not touching the boy.
You don't trust me.
You don't even like me.
You're right.
I don't trust you.
And I don't like you.
But you love your brother,
don't you?
But he's gonna be here with me.
So the kid lives.
Scout's honor. I don't blow
the little fucker's head off.
I didn't know I was on a
job with Mother Teresa.
Hello.
Anybody home?
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
Let's see how deep
this rabbit hole goes.
Hmm.
You see anything?
No. Nothing.
Surprised you trust me
enough to keep watch.
Well, I guess we're in this
together, aren't we?
What does that mean?
It means you and I both know
who we really robbed.
Mm.
Don't forget the murder part.
Is that how this works
for you, hmm?
You go from taking lives
to saving 'em?
When you're an army medic,
you get trained to do both.
Right. Okay.
That explains the watch.
You wear it backwards,
so the crystal face
doesn't reflect
the sunlight, right?
I'm impressed.
Army brat.
I mean, it seems like
a lifetime ago, but, yeah.
Yeah, I was in the rangers,
but, uh,
we'll leave it at that
before I really start bitching.
Worried I'd snitch?
No. We just all have
our own stories
and I don't wanna
bore you with mine.
But whatever you were discussing with our
former friend in the back of that pawnshop,
it wasn't the weather.
Guess I... I won't bore you
with mine either.
Vinny Van gogh here.
Easy now, kid.
Easy now.
Why don't you slide
those earbuds down for me?
That's it.
- Who are you?
- Oh.
I am the last person
you would ever wanna meet.
Please.
You shouldn't be here.
If it's money, I-I got money.
You can take it.
Just go. Please.
You got yourself a regular,
little funhouse down here, kid.
What else you got around here?
Oh.
Now, I really wanna know.
Please.
This isn't safe.
For who?
Yeah. Sorry.
I'm not that easy.
You gotta wine and dine me
before you try and fuck me, kid.
Besides, this place
has got me kinda curious.
Please. Go. Just go.
- Are you alone?
- Yes.
Hmm.
- I don't believe you.
- I don't lie.
Grandpa taught me never to lie.
Yeah.
All right. Well...
Let's put that little
theory to the test.
Start walking.
Look, when he gets back, you
know what that means for me.
- He's gonna kill me.
- Grace.
You and I both know it. But I
could go right now. I could leave.
- I can't let that happen.
- Why not?
I could just get outta here.
You'll never see me again.
- You can trust me. Please.
- Look,
I ain't gonna let anything
happen to you, all right?
Right. I don't really need
a white knight right now.
I just need you to let me go.
I can't. I'm sorry.
They're always sorry.
- Where the fuck's my brother?
- Hey!
You put that shotgun down, junior.
He went to check on the kid.
Bullshit. I heard you two talk,
and you said you were
gonna let her go.
Are you fucking deaf?
- Drop the gun now!
- Fuck you!
Hey, you either believe me
and lower that thing,
or I will put a bullet right
through your stupid brain.
And I won't miss.
All right. Whatever.
Just fucking...
Kill the lights.
What is it?
It's the kid's family.
What the fuck is that?
Jesus, is that a fucking person?
What is this place?
I knew something was off
about that kid.
Should've trusted my gut.
Please.
You gotta get outta here.
Shut the fuck up.
Whoa!
What are you into, kid?
Are you a little pervert?
Peeping Tom?
I don't know,
because this all seems
like you have a lot more than stashing
daddy's playboys under your bed.
Whatever it is...
I got a feeling you won't be
calling the cops on me now, will ya?
Please.
Just for your own sake.
For my own sake?
You see, in life,
we all have our
specialties, our talents.
Mine, other than torturing
and killing
little fucking kids...
My other one
is making people speak.
And since you are a kid...
I figure we can play
a little game.
You know, I haven't played
this in a while actually.
One more.
The odds are not good now, kid.
Let's go for a walk.
Where's Alex, man? He
should've been back by now.
Oh, shit.
- Hey, where are you going?
- To find Alex.
This job isn't done until he
delivers that cash to his boss.
I'm gonna make sure
that happens.
You don't even know
what you're dealing with here.
No, I don't. I guess
I'm gonna find out.
Keep eyes on her and the bag.
You're in control now.
We got problems.
Look, man. I'm sorry
about my brother.
He's fucking crazy.
Yeah, he is.
Is that gramps?
Let's see. Let's see
if you're serious, huh?
What the fuck? Fuck!
Fuck, Alex.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Grandpa!
- What the fuck? Fuck!
- Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
What the fuck was that?
Shit.
Piece of shit.
Fuck! Fuck.
Let's just go.
Just get outta here.
It wasn't you.
Just fucking go.
Just go! Just go! Go!
- Just fucking go!
- Where?
Come on, fuck you.
Fuck you!
Fuck you, bastard! Fuck!
God!
Shit. Shit.
Shit!
Help... me.
Grandpa!
No, no, no, no, no!
Please! She didn't do anything.
It's just the others!
No!
No. No.
Shane! Shane!
I don't want to die.
Shane!
Fuck! Fuck!
Let him go! Hey!
Hey, hey! Listen to me.
I got 100,000 dollars
back in that house.
Whatever you got going on,
you let us go right now,
and you can have it, okay?
Let us go.
Please, please, please, please.
Let us go, you motherfuckers!
You motherfuckers!
Fuck you!
My daughter.
She met a man like you.
He was a monster.
He was evil incarnate.
She stayed with him for the
kids, if you know what I mean...
Until I came,
and I collected all of them.
And I took them at night.
My daughter's life
was snuffed out
after she was brutalized
and murdered.
Do you know what her crime was?
Her crime was
that she had left him.
I'd gone to Santa fe.
She had stayed back with my
nine-year-old granddaughter
and my infant grandson.
We learned that this man was
incredibly cruel to children,
his own flesh and blood.
She had the most
wonderful smile.
I found the man that did it,
and I took my revenge on him.
I did it the way I saw fit.
She was our catch for the night.
But you...
You had to come here,
and ruin everything
I had planned.
We all do what we must
in times like these.
You have ruined
all of your organs
with all of that stuff
that you put into your body.
But...
Your eyes...
Your eyes,
they will fetch
a very high-price.
Vengeance, as you are aware,
is a very expensive business.
Prep him.
You shouldn't struggle.
Your blood pressure's elevated.
Danny... what are you...
What are you doing?
Well, your body
is in good condition.
The liver's
slightly damaged, but...
Danny? Listen to me.
What is this?
Danny, what is this?
Your body shows signs
of childbirth.
You're a mother.
I've never met a mother.
What do you mean?
What about your mom, Danny?
I don't remember my mom.
A daughter, Danny.
Yeah. Um...
I had a daughter, Danny.
Had?
Danny, what is this?
Danny, what is this place?
What is this?
- I wanted to warn you.
- No.
But I couldn't.
The last time I did,
they were...
He was so angry.
- Who?
- Grandpa.
He does it for me.
Him and Jodi.
Listen, Danny.
Okay.
Look, listen.
Um, I don't understand.
I don't know what this is, okay?
I-I don't understand.
He helps people.
That's what he does.
He takes what people waste, and
gives it to more deserving people.
Uh, what do you mean by that?
What-what does he take, Danny?
What does he... Danny,
what does he take, Danny?
Wait. Listen.
Hey! Hey!
Hey, can you hear me?
Please!
God, no,
what did they do to him?
Can you hear me? Hey! Hey!
Oh, fuck.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
I really am.
You seem nice.
Because I am nice.
Danny, it's because
I am nice. 'Cause I am...
I am a nice person.
Just... what does he take?
What does... What is this place?
Just talk to me, please.
Just tell me
what's going on here, okay?
- No. Danny, just tell me.
- I asked him, begged him.
- Look at me, Danny.
- Said not to hurt you.
You don't deserve to be hurt.
He agreed to that, at least.
No. No, no, no.
Danny. Hey.
Hey, Danny!
No.
Luna. Luna.
My daughter's name was Luna.
It's been three years now.
She died?
Look, I-i...
I lost myself, okay?
I don't even know
who I am anymore.
But, Danny, I am trying.
I am trying here, okay?
I'm trying, please, Danny.
- He'll make it quick.
- No, no, Danny. No!
Danny! Danny!
He ain't coming back.
What is this place?
This place.
If I knew, I'd tell ya.
And the others?
Haven't seen 'em.
We gotta get the fuck
outta here now,
or we're done.
Okay.
I'm coming.
I'm coming. Fucking...
We gotta get outta here.
Please.
I got it. I got it.
I'm coming.
Try... try to...
- Try to just pull it! Just try to pull it.
- Hold on. I'm coming.
- It's going too far. Please.
- I can't pull it.
- Please, please, please.
- I gotta snap the fucking...
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Hold on. Hold on!
Hold on.
- Quickly.
- I got it.
- I'm gonna snap it.
- Okay, okay, okay. Just do it. Just do it.
- Please. Please.
- Almost got it. Almost got it.
- I'm gonna snap the fucking thing.
- Okay.
Fuck you!
Wait. Hey, one second. Please.
No, no, no! Hey! Stop!
Fucking wait!
Alex?
What the hell?
They took my fucking eyes?
Alex, where's Shane?
It's fucked.
Fucking crazy person.
What are you fucking
monsters doing? Huh?
You motherfuckers.
You motherfuckers!
Fetch the girl. Now.
Mm. Mine.
I have no need for his body.
- Play.
- Hmm.
I believe you deserve
the reward.
Have fun, my dear.
Hmm.
Fuckers! Motherfuckers!
Alex!
Cody!
Where the fuck did you go?
He's ready for you.
Danny, look.
Danny, you don't have
to do this, okay?
Whatever's happened
in the past, it's okay.
It's okay.
You can stop this.
So many people have been hurt.
It's okay.
You can stop this. Please.
Please stop it, Danny.
- Please.
- We have to go.
No, Danny. No.
Please. Fuck.
Danny...
We can run away.
- What?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you and me
together. We...
We could leave this
place together, you know?
You know I can't do that.
Yes. You can, Danny.
Yes, you can.
Wait...
You still with me?
I'm with ya.
Very good.
Look. Look, you don't have
to do this. Okay?
I know I don't have to.
Organ harvesting, right?
That's what this shit is.
I save people's lives.
Not like you, who wastes the
gifts that you've been given.
But not in my hands.
What gives you the right to decide
who gets to live and who dies? Hmm?
Somebody made that choice
for my daughter
many years ago.
Danny's mother.
Don't listen to him, okay?
Don't. Look at me.
Now, I make the choice.
The good live.
They live using the organs
from scum like you,
who would do nothing
but waste them.
Bullshit.
It's bullshit,
your whole fucking plan.
Tell me.
Have you ever known
how long it takes
for somebody who's waiting
for a new organ?
Seven years.
Most people have died
before they get them,
when one murderer,
one drug addict
could save six good people.
You think you're
fucking god, don't you?
No. No, I don't think
I'm god.
I think I know what we
have to pay for our sins.
And it should be
in flesh and blood.
No, you're a sick, old man.
That's what you are.
You do what you want with me.
You let her go.
You hear me?
You let her go!
Her?
Your womb
will give a child to someone...
Who will be a good mother.
And what's your cut, huh?
Well, you know,
we all want to make
a living, don't we?
Yeah, exactly. Fuck.
What do you want?
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
The fuck?
I can move.
I get it.
Now.
You wanna play some games.
All right.
Let's play
some motherfucking games.
Fuck.
Yeah. I like to play.
You wanna play rough, huh?
You wanna play some games,
you fucking freak?
Huh?
Oh!
Oh, you're a big girl, huh?
You mute bitch.
Danny.
Music, please.
Danny, look.
You motherfucker!
Fuck you.
It doesn't have to be
this way, okay? Listen.
It doesn't have to be like this.
Danny, look at me.
Hey, Danny.
Don't listen to her, son.
Don't listen.
It's all lies.
Fuck.
Fuck you.
Fucking pig.
Oh, fuck you,
you stupid old man!
Excellent.
Now, the fun begins.
Grandpa!
- Fuck you, bitch!
- Grandpa, you okay?
You!
It's a waste of a body!
Jesus Christ.
Let me in!
Okay.
- I can't move.
- Come on.
I can't feel my legs.
That won't hold her off
for long.
Come on. There must be
something you can do, okay?
Can you...
Check the drawers.
Drawers here.
See if you can find
a surgical stapler.
What have you done?
Danny, come on. All right?
I'm not fucking dying.
If I'm going out,
I'm going on my own terms.
Oh, fuck.
She'll kill all of us!
All right, then you're gonna help me
get us out of here. Okay? Come on!
I can't.
I can't... and you go...
I don't know.
Kid, you're getting her
the fuck outta here, okay?
That's it.
Come here.
Bring it over here.
Let me see. Let me see.
- Okay.
- That's it.
All right. It's simple.
Works just like a stapler.
You're gonna push the edges
of my skin together.
Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah. Go for it.
Good.
Follow. Nice.
Good. Keep going.
Great.
Okay. Now, help me
get him up, okay?
- No, you can't carry me. It's not gonna work.
- But I can try.
God, fuck!
Is there another way
out of here?
We gotta go!
Okay. Well, I'm not gonna just
fucking leave him, Danny, okay?
You're leaving me.
I'm gonna buy you some time.
Grab his gun.
Get his gun.
You're gonna leave.
All right.
You see the needles?
Yeah. There they are.
It should be adrenaline.
You gotta pump it
right into me, okay?
Maybe it'll help me move.
- Give me some strength.
- Where?
Right where my heart is.
You good with that?
- Okay.
- Do it!
- We have to go.
- Come on.
Go. Now, go!
I don't even know your name.
Cody.
- Okay. Cody.
- Get out.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
How's that, huh?
Fuck!
Fuck.
Go!
Help me with this!
Danny! Run, run! Danny!
Run! Go! Now!
Please...
Danny?
Danny!
Danny, Danny!
- Danny! Danny!
- No!
Danny!
No! No!
My brother...
Hey.
Okay, okay, okay.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Where do we go from here?
No idea.
Wanna find out?